# KATHERINE PACHECO

I'm Katherine Pacheco, a passionate Fullstack Developer. I like art and technology and considerer myself a self taught person. During the pandemic I started programming and I found what I like.

I have more than 2 years and half working as a fullstack developer using React, React-Native, CSS, Tailwind, Styled Components, TS, NodeJS, Express and also I have skills in adobe suite

# TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS

- Typescript, Javascript, React, NextJS, React Native, Angular, Bootstrap, CSS, Styled Components, Chakra, MUI, Tailwind.
- Node, Express, Passport,
  Postgresql, Sequelize, NestJS,
  Socket.io, Stripe, Firebase.
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premier, Adobe After Effects.
- Logic Pro, Ableton Live
- English B2

# **EDUCATION**

## CODING BOOTCAMP

Plataforma 5 | 09/2021 - 12/2021

800 hr's bootcamp about web development with methodology SCRUM.

 Tech: Javascript, React, React Native, Bootstrap, CSS, Node, Express, Passport, Postgress, Sequelize.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

BAJA TECHNOLOGIES | MEXICO | 06/2022 - 08/2023

Worked as a Software Developer using Javascript, Typescript, React, React Native, Tailiwind, CSS, Git, Next JS, Firebase to create software products

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

JUSTA COMPANY | GERMANY | 06/2023 - 09/2023

Worked as a Software Developer using Typescript, React, Zustand, AWS, Tailwind, Vite, Git.

#### REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER

IT-Techgroup | Argentina | 02/2022 - 04/2022

Worked as a React Native Developer using Javascript, React Native, Firebase, AWS, Tailwind, Git.